Guide to the Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files, 1950-2010 (bulk 1977-1986)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IX. Additions
  - Lindbloom, Nancy Willard, 1965-1987; (1 folder) (Folder 42.19)
  - Lipschutz, Elaine C., 1980-1984 (Folder 42.20)
  - Lipschulz, Ilse Hempel (Mrs. Lewis D.), 1962-1986 (Folder 42.21)
  - Livingston, Kenneth R., 1977-1985 (Folder 42.22)
  - Lowry, Richard J., 1967-1986 (Folder 42.23)
  - Lunt, William E., 1974-1984 (Folder 42.24)
  - Mace, Dean T., 1955-1983 (Folder 42.25)
  - MacKenzie, Marlo O., 1973-1988 (Folder 42.26)
  - Mallon, Thomas, 1979-1988 (Folder 42.27)
  - Mamiya, Lawrence Hiroshi, 1975-1985 (Folder 42.28)
  - Marshall, Natalie Junemann, 1964-1979 (Folder 42.29)
  - Merriell, David M., 1968-1983 (Folder 42.30)
  - Miller, Mitchell H., 1972-1986 (Folder 42.31)
  - Miringoff, Marque L., 1976-1985 (Folder 42.32)
  - Moore, Deborah Dash, 1976-1988 (Folder 42.33)
  - Morgan, Susan, 1980-1985 (Folder 42.34)
  - Mucci, Joseph F., 1965-1982 (Folder 42.35)
  - Murray, Michael, 1970-1988 (Folder 42.36)
  - McAulay, Robert, 1982 (Folder 42.37)
  - McCarthy, Michael, 1968-1988 (Folder 42.38)
  - McCleary, John H., 1975-1986 (Folder 42.39)
  - McHugh, Thomas F., 1974-1988 (Folder 42.40)
  - McCloskey, Susan, 1977-1985 (Folder 42.41)
  - Mehaffey, Leathem, 1973-1986 (Folder 42.42)
  - Olsen, Donald J., 1964-1987 (Folder 42.43)
  - Page, Barbara Joan, 1969-1986 (Folder 42.44)
  - Barbara Page (Confidential), 1984 (Folder 42.45)
  - Parks, Robert E., 1976-1981 (Folder 42.46)
  - Peck, H. Daniel, 1980-1985 (Folder 42.47)
  - Periolat-Czula, Jeanne, 1975-1979 (Folder 42.48)
  - Pierce, Charles E. (Jr.), 1970-1986 (Folder 42.49)
  - Pin, Emile Jean, 1972-1985 (Folder 42.50)
  - Pommer, Richard, 1966-1979 (Folder 42.51)
  - Pounder, Robert Lachlan, 1972-1988 (Folder 42.52)
  - Puglisi, Roberta, 1987 (Folder 42.53)
  - Rappaport, Rhoda, 1961-1981 (Folder 42.54)
  - Reilly, Edward R., 1970-1987 (Folder 42.55)
  - Reno, Christine, 1972-1985 (Folder 42.56)
  - Riley, Joyce B., 1971-1987 (Folder 42.57)
  - Ringle, Martin, 1978-1984 (Folder 42.58)
  - Roseman, Harry, 1987 (Folder 42.59)
  - Rothwell, William F., 1963-1986 (Folder 42.60)
  - Rousseas Stephen W., 1969-1989 (Folder 42.61)
  - Rumble, Wilfrid (Jr), 1961-1984 (Folder 42.62)
  - Sadowsky, Stephen, 1968-1986 (Folder 42.63)
  - Schalk, David L., 1968-1986 (Folder 42.64)
  - Schlessman, Mark A., 1980-1985 (Folder 42.65)
  - Shanley, Mary Lyndon, 1973-1988 (Folder 42.66)
  - Shultz, Herbert L., 1974-1981 (Folder 42.67)
  - Silverman, Sondra, 1980-1986 (Folder 42.68)
  - Silverman Support Letters, 1986 (Folder 42.69)
  - Smith, Henrietta T., 1965-1985 (Folder 42.70)
  - Smith, Mary Caroll, 1978-1986 (Folder 42.71)
  - Smith, Virginia B., 1977-1978 (Folder 42.72)
  - Sprichorn, Evert M., 1964-1985 (Folder 42.73)
  - Stearns, Robert, 1961-1988 (Folder 42.74)
  - Steerman, James B., 1967-1989 (Folder 42.75)
  - Stern, Lilo, 1968-1985 (Folder 42.76)
  - Stillman, Peter G., 1970-1983 (Folder 42.77)
  - Suter, Robert B., 1977-1981 (Folder 42.78)
  - Tavel, Morton, 1967-1985 (Folder 42.79)
  - Thompson III, Alexander M., 1977-1981 (Folder 42.80)
  - Toegel, Edith, 1969-1984 (Folder 42.81)
  - Uribe, Blanca, 1969-1984 (Folder 42.82)
  - Vander Veer, Garrett L., 1965-1985 (Folder 42.83)
  - Vander Veer, Delma (Mrs Garrett), 1968-1979 (Folder 42.84)
  - Villamoare, Adelaide H., 1975-1986 (Folder 43.1)
  - Vorobiov, Masha N., 1977-1982 (Folder 43.2)
  - Wallace, Patricia B., 1976-1989 (Folder 43.3)
  - Willey, Richard J., 1964-1990 (Folder 43.4)
  - Williams, Donald, 1961-1981 (Folder 43.5)
  - Wilson, Richard, 1966-1988 (Folder 43.6)
  - Wilson, Sandra A. (Chaplain), 1975-1984 (Folder 43.7)
  - Wohl, Anthony S., 1963-1986 (Folder 43.8)
  - Zorzoli, Anita, 1982-1983 (Folder 43.9)
  - Adlmann, Jan (Art Gallery), 1985-1990 (Folder 43.10)
  - Africana Studies, 1986-1989 (Folder 43.11)
  - American Culture, 1987-1988 (Folder 43.12)
  - Anthropology, 1987-1989 (Folder 43.13)
  - Art, 1986-1989 (Folder 43.14)
  - Art Department, 1985-1986 (Folder 43.15)
  - Art Gallery Needs, 1986-1988 (Folder 43.16)
  - Museums in Academe — Frances D. Fergusson: Panel 2, Nov 1986 (Folder 43.17)
  - Museum Development, 1987-1989 (Folder 43.18)
  - Vassar Collection USIA Tour Proposal (Latin America), 1986-1987 (Folder 43.19)
  - Exhibition Schedule, 1986-1987 (Folder 43.20)
  - Museum Assessment by AAM, 1984 (Folder 43.21)
  - New College Museums Symposium/Vassar, Nov 1986 (Folder 43.22)
  - Art Gallery — Exhibits/Brochures, 1986-1989 (Folder 43.23)
  - Taylor Hall Addition Preliminary Study, 1980-1982 (Folder 43.24)
  - Art Gallery, 1986-1988 (Folder 43.25)
  - Asian Studies/Asian Languages, 1989 (Folder 43.26)
  - Biology, 1985-1989 (Folder 43.27)
  - Biology Department profiles for President Fergusson (Folder 43.28)
  - Chemistry, 1987-1988 (Folder 43.29)
  - Classics, 1986-1987 (Folder 43.30)
  - Cognitive Studies, 1981-1989 (Folder 43.31)
  - Computer Science, 1986-1989 (Folder 43.32)
  - Drama, 1987-1989 (Folder 43.33)
  - Economics, 1987-1988 (Folder 43.34)
  - Education, 1988 (Folder 43.35)
  - Education — Self Study, 1983-1984; (6 folders) (Folders 43.36-43.41)
  - English, 1986-1988 (Folder 43.42)
  - French, 1988-1990 (Folder 43.43)
  - Geography, 1987 (Folder 43.44)
  - Geology, 1986-1989 (Folder 43.45)
  - German, 1986-1989 (Folder 43.46)
  - Hispanic Studies, 1987-1989 (Folder 44.1)
  - History, 1986-1990 (Folder 44.2)
  - International Studies, 1988 (Folder 44.3)
  - Mathematics, 1986-1989 (Folder 44.4)
  - Multidisciplinary Programs, 1987 (Folder 44.5)
  - Music, 1986-1989 (Folder 44.6)
  - Philosophy, 1987-1988 (Folder 44.7)
  - Physics/Astronomy, 1987-1988 (Folder 44.8)
  - Psychology, 1988 (Folder 44.9)
  - Physical Education/Dance, 1979-1989 (Folder 44.10)
  - Athletics, 1985-1989 (Folder 44.11)
  - Political Science, 1982-1989 (Folder 44.12)
  - Religion, 1988 (Folder 44.13)
  - Russian, 1987-1988 (Folder 44.14)
  - Women’s College, 1986-1987 (Folder 44.15)
  - Faculty Compensation Committee, 1985-1987 (Folder 44.16)
  - Department Chairmen and Program Directors, 1985-1990 (Folder 44.17)
  - Faculty Committees — General, 1984-1989 (Folder 44.18)
  - Committee on Committees, 1979-1989 (Folder 44.19)
  - House Fellows, 1980-1988 (Folder 44.20)
  - Meeting with Committee on Committees, May 1986 (Folder 44.21)
  - Committee on Committees Meeting, Mar 1985 (Folder 44.22)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies (A), 1986-1987 (Folder 44.23)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies (B), 1986-1988 (Folder 44.24)
  - Faculty Leaves, 1987-1988 (Folder 44.25)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1984-1986 (Folder 44.26)
  - Faculty Meeting (VBS), May 1986 (Folder 44.27)
  - FASC — Schedule of Faculty Reviews (President Smith), 1985-1986 (Folder 44.28)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Folder 44.29)
  - Faculty Meeting (VBS), Oct 1985 (Folder 44.30)
  - Faculty Meeting (VBS), Sep 1985 (Folder 44.31)
  - Faculty Meeting (VBS), May 1985 (Folder 44.32)
  - Faculty Policy and Conference Committee (FPCC), 1983-1984 (Folder 44.33)
  - Meeting with FPCC, Apr 1983 (Folder 44.34)
  - Faculty Publications/Activities (Folder 44.35)
  - Faculty Mailing List (Folder 44.36)
  - FASC, 1984-1985 (Folder 44.37)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1986-1988 (Folder 44.38)
  - Academic Resource Center, 1984-1987 (Folder 44.39)
  - Academic Freedom, 1987 (Folder 44.40)
  - Promotion/Tenure Letters, 1984 (Folder 44.41)
  - Leaves, 1986-1987 (Folder 44.42)
  - Leaves, 1985-1986 (Folder 44.43)
  - Jennings, Andrew (FF Attention), 1986 (Folder 44.44)
  - House Fellows, 1987-1988 (Folder 44.45)
  - Department Chairmen and Program Directors, 1984-1985 (Folder 44.46)
  - Department Chairmen and Program Directors, 1983-1984 (Folder 44.47)
  - Department Chairmen and Program Directors, 1982-1983 (Folder 44.48)
  - Department Chairmen and Program Directors, 1980-1982 (Folder 44.49)
  - Chairmen’s Handbook, 1971-1986 (Folder 44.50)
  - Faculty Handbooks, 1980-1986 (Folder 44.51)
  - Africana Studies, 1983-1985 (Folder 45.1)
  - Africana Studies, 1979 (Folder 45.2)
  - American Culture, 1981-1983 (Folder 45.3)
  - Nicaragua Trip — Randolph D. Pope, 1984-1986 (Folder 45.4)
  - Anthropology-Sociology, 1976-1983 (Folder 45.5)
  - Chinese Art Exhibition, 1986 (Folder 45.6)
  - Art Gallery Director, 1982 (Folder 45.7)
  - Jan Earnst Adlmann — Interview for Position of Art Gallery Director, Jun, 1985 (Folder 45.8)
  - Art Gallery — Candidate for Registrar/Curatorial, 1985 (Folder 45.9)
  - Art Gallery, 1984-1986 (Folder 45.10)
  - Art Gallery, 1986 (Folder 45.11)
  - K. Porter Aichele — Interview for Position of Art Gallery Director, Jun 1985 (Folder 45.12)
  - Richard Beard — Interview for Position of Art Gallery Director, Jun 1985 (Folder 45.13)
  - James Mundy — Interview for Position of Art Gallery Director, Jun 1985 (Folder 45.14)
  - Patricia Condon — Interview for Position of Art Gallery Director, Jun 1985 (Folder 45.15)
  - Gail Levin — Art Gallery Director Position, Jun 1985 (Folder 45.16)
  - Art Gallery — Director, 1985 (Folder 45.17)
  - Art Gallery, 1978-1983 (Folder 45.18)
  - Art Gallery — Candidates for the Position of “Director”, 1982 (Folder 45.19)
  - Art Gallery — Jades, 1976-1981 (Folder 45.20)
  - Sarcophagus, 1981 (Folder 45.21)
  - Art Departments, 1977-1984 (Folder 45.22)
  - Audio-Visual Resource Center, 1980 (Folder 45.23)
  - Biology — Ad Hoc Summer Research Program, 1985-1986 (Folder 45.24)
  - Biology Department, 1978-1986 (Folder 45.25)
  - Christine Milcarek — Candidate for Associate Professor (Biology Department), Sep 1982 (Folder 45.26)
  - Chemistry Department, 1979-1985 (Folder 45.27)
  - Classics Department, 1977-1980 (Folder 45.28)
  - Computer Science Department, 1985 (Folder 45.29)
  - Drama Department, 1979-1984 (Folder 45.30)
  - Drama Department, 1981 (Folder 45.31)
  - Drama Department, 1978-1981 (Folder 45.32)
  - Mary Virginia Heinlein Theater, 1973-1977 (Folder 45.33)
  - The Jean Webster McKinney Papers, 1977 (Folder 45.34)
  - Economics Department, 1977-1981 (Folder 45.35)
  - Education Department Self Study, 1983 (Folder 45.36)
  - Education Department, 1977-1985 (Folder 45.37)
  - English Department, 1976-1985 (Folder 45.38)
  - French Department, 1977-1978 (Folder 45.39)
  - Geology-Geography Department, 1976-1985 (Folder 45.40)
  - German Department, 1976-1978 (Folder 45.41)
  - Health Department, 1976-1979 (Folder 45.42)
  - Hispanic Studies Department, 1977-1982 (Folder 45.43)
  - History Department, 1976-1984 (Folder 45.44)
  - Italian Department, 1977-1982 (Folder 45.45)
  - Library, 1978-1981 (Folder 45.46)
  - Cornaro Tercentenary, 1974-1980 (Folder 45.47)
  - Founding Friends of the Library, 1972-1977 (Folder 45.48)
  - Library — “The Great Window”, 1972-1976 (Folder 45.49)
  - H.D. Lockwood Appreciation Booklet Committee, 1952-1976 (Folder 45.50)
  - Mathematics Department, 1976-1984 (Folder 45.51)
  - Music Department, 1976-1985 (Folder 45.52)
  - Madrigal Singers Trip, 1984-1986 (Folder 45.53)
  - Report of the Director of Choral Activities, Dec 10, 1979 (Folder 45.54)
  - Philosophy Department, 1976-1982 (Folder 46.1)
  - Physical Education, 1972-1985 (Folder 46.2)
  - Physics-Astronomy Department, 1977-1986 (Folder 46.3)
  - Political Science Department, 1976-1983 (Folder 46.4)
  - Nursery School, 1977-1979 (Folder 46.5)
  - Psychology Department, 1976-1986 (Folder 46.6)
  - Russian Department, 1977-1979 (Folder 46.7)
  - American Culture Department, 1976-1979 (Folder 46.8)
  - Africana Studies, 1969-1982 (Folder 46.9)
  - Computer Science Studies, 1976-1981 (Folder 46.10)
  - East Asian Studies Department, 1975-1979 (Folder 46.11)
  - Science, Technology and Society (STS), 1978-1980 (Folder 46.12)
  - Women’s Studies, 1980-1986 (Folder 46.13)
  - Women’s Studies, 1981-1983 (Folder 46.14)
  - Women’s Studies Department, 1978-1979 (Folder 46.15)
  - Women’s Studies, 1975-1978 (Folder 46.16)
  - Annual Report of the Dean of the College, 1983-1984 (Folder 46.17)
  - Department Annual Reports (Loose Files), 1985-1986 (Folder 46.18)
  - Faculty Salary Budget, 1979-1980 (Folder 46.19)
  - Contracts, 1968-1969 (Folder 46.20)
  - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Folder 46.21)
  - Contracts, 1970-1971 (Folder 46.22)
  - Contracts, 1971-1972 (Folder 46.23)
  - Contracts, 1972-1973 (Folder 47.1)
  - Contracts, 1973-1974 (Folder 47.2)
  - Contracts, 1974-1975 (Folder 47.3)
  - Contracts, 1975-1976 (Folder 47.4)
  - Contracts, 1976-1977 (Folder 47.5)
  - Contracts, 1977-1978 (Folder 47.6)
  - Contracts, 1978-1979 (Folder 47.7)
  - Contracts, 1979-1980 (Folder 47.8)
  - Contracts (Faculty), 1980-1981 (Folder 47.9)
  - Faculty Contracts, 1981-1982 (Folder 47.10)
  - Faculty Contracts, 1982-1983 (Folder 47.11)
  - Current Faculty, 1968-1969 (Folder 47.12)
  - Current Faculty, 1969-1970 (Folder 47.13)
  - Current Faculty, 1970-1971 (Folder 47.14)
  - Current Faculty, 1971-1972 (Folder 47.15)
  - Current Faculty, 1972-1973 (Folder 47.16)
  - Current Faculty, 1973-1974 (Folder 47.17)
  - Current Faculty, 1974-1975 (Folder 47.18)
  - Current Faculty, 1975-1976 (Folder 47.19)
  - Current Faculty, 1976-1977 (Folder 47.20)
  - New Appointments, 1979-1980 (Folder 47.21)
  - Governance — Amendments, 1951-1979 (Folder 47.22)
  - VC — A Self-Study Report, Feb 1979 (Folder 48.1)
  - Report of the Comprehensive Planning Committee, Sep 1968 (Folder 48.2)
  - Handbook for Institutional Self-Study, 1977 (Folder 48.3)
  - Study of Financial Equilibrium for Vassar College (Draft), Dec 31, 1981 (Folder 48.4)
  - Study of Financial Equilibrium for Vassar College (Final Draft), Apr 20, 1982 (Folder 48.5)
  - Summary Report on Achieving Financial Equilibrium for VC (Draft), Apr 20, 1982 (Folder 48.6)
  - Cambridge Associates, Inc., 1979-1981 (Folder 48.7)
  - Cambridge Associates, Inc. Meeting, Nov 1981 (Folder 48.8)
  - VC — A Self-Report — Draft, Jan 1979 (Folder 48.9)
  - Study of Financial Equilibrium for Vassar College (Final Draft), Jan 28, 1982 (Folder 48.10)
  - Study for Financial Equilibrium for Vassar College (Final Draft), Apr 5, 1982 (Folder 48.11)
  - Commencement Speech, 1984 (Folder 48.12)
  - Tenure Ratios/Transparencies (Folder 48.13)
  - Cambridge Report, May 15, 1982 (Folder 48.14)
  - Powerhouse Theater (Folder 48.15)
  - Davidoff (SDR Marketing, Inc.), 1983-1984 (Folder 48.16)
  - Request for Proposal for Administrative Computer Software, 1983 (Folder 48.17)
  - William F. Buckley Jr. Correspondence — Completed Responses, 1980 (Folder 48.18)
  - Buckley Petition and President’s April 21 Statement, 1980 (Folder 48.19)
  - Faculty Support Buckley — Open Letter, 1980 (Folder 48.20)
  - Buckley Correspondence — Extra Set of Letters, 1980 (Folder 48.21)
  - The William F. Buckley Story, 1980 (Folder 48.22)
  - Buckley, Jr., William M. — Background, 1978-1980 (Folder 48.23)
  - Buckley/Partial Clips, 1980 (Folder 48.24)
  - Lisa Browar — Interview, Nov 1981 (Folder 48.25)
  - Affirmative Action Report, 1976 (Folder 48.26)
  - Africana Studies Program, 1981-1982 (Folder 48.27)
  - 1980 Black Caucus, 1980-1982 (Folder 48.28)
  - Black Students Guide to Colleges, 1982 (Folder 48.29)
  - Brochures — Other Colleges, 1982 (Folder 48.30)
  - Brooks’ Report, 1982 (Folder 48.31)
  - Catlin Report, 1970 (Folder 48.32)
  - Comparable Data, 1980-1982 (Folder 48.33)
  - Financial Aid — Blacks (Folder 48.34)
  - Hodges 1979 Memo, 1979-1982 (Folder 48.35)
  - Hodges’ Statement, 1982 (Folder 48.36)
  - Minority Faculty, 1979-1980 (Folder 48.37)
  - Minority National Data, 1978-1980 (Folder 48.38)
  - Outline — Minority Committee, 1982-1983 (Folder 48.39)
  - Secundy Letter, 1982 (Folder 48.40)
  - Vassar Black Alumnae/I, 1982 (Folder 48.41)
  - Vassar Data — Enrollment, 1982 (Folder 48.42)
  - Transparencies, 1983 (Folder 48.43)
  - Assembly Intern Program, 1985 (Folder 49.1)
  - International Film Festival, 1985 (Folder 49.2)
  - Africana Studies, 1985 (Folder 49.3)
  - “After Nairobi”, 1985-1986 (Folder 49.4)
  - Accuracy in Academia, 1985 (Folder 49.5)
  - Appeal Committee, 1985 (Folder 49.6)
  - Maguire/Ford Foundation, 1984 (Folder 49.7)
  - New York Times Selective Guide to Colleges, 1983-1986 (Folder 49.8)
  - Murphy Farm, 1981-1982 (Folder 49.9)
  - Swain Farm, 1984-1985 (Folder 49.10)
  - Oberlin Report, 1986-1987 (Folder 49.11)
  - Oberlin Science Project, 1984-1987 (Folder 49.12)
  - Oberlin Science Conference, 1985-1987 (Folder 49.13)
  - Oberlin — Cell Group Program, 1985-1986 (Folder 49.14)
  - Residence/Overcrowding Problem, 1983-1984 (Folder 49.15)
  - PAG/Professional Development, 1985 (Folder 49.16)
  - Robert Parks, 1985 (Folder 49.17)
  - Alice Paul Papers (Folder 49.18)
  - Personnel Clarifications, 1981 (Folder 49.19)
  - PH.D. Productivity, 1985 (Folder 49.20)
  - Part-Time Faculty, 1981-1984 (Folder 49.21)
  - Pratt House, 1981-1988 (Folder 49.22)
  - Political Action Policy, 1984 (Folder 49.23)
  - Portrait of President Smith, 1986 (Folder 49.24)
  - President’s Distinguished Visitor Program — Invitations, 1981-1987 (Folder 49.25)
  - Presidential Evaluation Procedure, 1982-1985 (Folder 49.26)
  - Presidential Review/References (2), 1985 (Folder 49.27)
  - Presidential Review Motion, 1984-1985 (Folder 49.28)
  - President’s Review References, 1984 (Folder 49.29)
  - Public/Private Projects, 1983-1985 (Folder 49.30)
  - Questionnaire Matter, 1984 (Folder 49.31)
  - Sarah Lawrence Meeting, 1986 (Folder 49.32)
  - Seven College Conference, 1985 (Folder 49.33)
  - Sexual Orientation Policy, 1982-1983 (Folder 49.34)
  - Sloan Proposals, 1985 (Folder 49.35)
  - Cognitive Science — Sloan Foundation, 1980-1984 (Folder 49.36)
  - Staff/Unionizing — Contract Agreements, 1985-1986 (Folder 49.37)
  - Alison Stokes (Confidential) (2), 1982-1985 (Folder 49.38)
  - Alison Stokes (Confidential) (1), 1982-1984 (Folder 49.39)
  - Student Housing, 1983-1985 (Folder 49.40)
  - Student Activities Office, 1983 (Folder 49.41)
  - Student Housing, 1983-1985 (Folder 49.42)
  - Studio Art Major, 1981-1984 (Folder 49.43)
  - Summer Theater, 1983-1985 (Folder 49.44)
  - South Africa, 1985 (Folder 50.1)
  - South Africa, 1985 (Folder 50.2)
  - South Africa (2), 1985-1986 (Folder 50.3)
  - South African Research Consortium, 1985 (Folder 50.4)
  - Tenure Ratio, 1984-1985 (Folder 50.5)
  - Trustee Actions on South Africa Investments, 1978-1979 (Folder 50.6)
  - “Time Capsule”, 1983 (Folder 50.7)
  - “Under 19”, 1984 (Folder 50.8)
  - Wagner, Ana Maria, 1985 (Folder 50.9)
  - Writer-In-Residence Program, 1982-1983 (Folder 50.10)
  - Women’s Equity, 1984 (Folder 50.11)
  - Kaurouma, Pat, 1985-1986; (1 folder) (Folder 50.12)
  - Silverman — Letters, 1986-1987 (Folder 50.13)
  - Silverman — Litigation, 1987 (Folder 50.14)
  - Sondra Silverman #3, 1986-1987 (Folder 50.15)
  - Silverman, Sondra, 1986-1987 (Folder 50.16)
  - Faculty Elections, 1983-1985 (Folder 50.17)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Social, 1984 (Folder 50.18)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt, 1983-1985 (Folder 50.19)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Centennial Conference, 1983-1985 (Folder 50.20)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Centennial Conference, 1982-1984 (Folder 50.21)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt and Human Rights, 1981 (Folder 50.22)
  - The Eleanor Roosevelt Institute, 1975-1985 (Folder 50.23)
  - Retirement, 1983 (Folder 50.24)
  - A — General, 1981-1985 (Folder 50.25)
  - Administrative Retreat, 1981 (Folder 50.26)
  - Administrative Retreat, 1980 (Folder 50.27)
  - Adipose Tissue Satellite — VBS Welcome, Oct 1983 (Folder 50.28)
  - Admissions Workshop, Aug 1983; (1 folder) (Folder 50.29)
  - Admissions Candidate, 1985 (Folder 50.30)
  - Jolivette, Murray, 1985 (Folder 50.31)
  - Admissions — Robert Thornton, 1984 (Folder 50.32)
  - Office of Admission, 1976-1980 (Folder 50.33)
  - Administrative Workshop, 1982 (Folder 50.34)
  - Alumni Admission Workshop, Sep 1982 (Folder 50.35)
  - Application for Employment, 1983-1984 (Folder 51.1)
  - Art Gallery Review, 1978-1982 (Folder 51.2)
  - Friends of the Art Gallery, 1980-1985 (Folder 51.3)
  - Arts and Humanities Conference — NYC, Apr 1984 (Folder 51.4)
  - Astin, Alexander W., 1983 (Folder 51.5)
  - Athletics, 1980-1985 (Folder 51.6)
  - Barnes and Roche, Inc., 1980-1981 (Folder 51.7)
  - Barnes and Roche — Report on Case Testing and Feasibility, 1979 (Folder 51.8)
  - The Barton-Gillet Letter, 1983 (Folder 51.9)
  - Berkshire Conference of Women Historians, 1981-1983 (Folder 51.10)
  - Berkshire Conference of Women Historians, 1978-1979 (Folder 51.11)
  - Berkshire Conference of Women Historians, 1979-1980 (Folder 51.12)
  - Bishop Day Celebration (A) — Plans and Invitation, 1982-1983 (Folder 51.13)
  - Bishop Day Celebration (B) — Plans, 1982 (Folder 51.14)
  - Elizabeth Bishop Day, Apr 24, 1982 (Folder 51.15)
  - Bishop Papers, 1980-1982 (Folder 51.16)
  - Bishop Papers (A), 1978-1979 (Folder 51.17)
  - Bishop Papers (B), 1979-1980 (Folder 51.18)
  - Bishop Papers/Press Release, 1980-1981 (Folder 51.19)
  - Bishop Letters — Purchase from Dr. Anny Baumann, 1982-1984 (Folder 51.20)
  - Bishop Day (Follow-Up), 1982-1983 (Folder 51.21)
  - Bishop Day Celebration (Returns) 1, 1982 (Folder 51.22)
  - Bishop Day Celebration (Returns) 2, 1982 (Folder 51.23)
  - Black Affairs, 1982 (Folder 51.24)
  - Black Affairs, 1978-1980 (Folder 51.25)
  - Black Caucus, 1980 (Folder 51.26)
  - Black Youth and Education Panel, Feb 1985 (Folder 51.27)
  - Black Career Forum, 1983 (Folder 51.28)
  - Black Scientists, 1980 (Folder 51.29)
  - Blodgett Hall Auditorium, 1984 (Folder 51.30)
  - Braniff — Refund Claim — Dixie, 1983 (Folder 51.31)
  - Budget Sheets, 1983 (Folder 51.32)
  - Budget — Comptroller’s Report, 1980-1981 (Folder 51.33)
  - Dinner for Mr. Beye — Blegen Professor, Sep 1983 (Folder 51.34)
  - Calendar Items, 1980-1982 (Folder 51.35)
  - Mr. Jack Reitzes (Interview) — Executive Director, Career Development and Field Work, 1983 (Folder 51.36)
  - Mr. Peter M. Rainey (Interview) — Executive Director, Career Development and Field Work, 1983 (Folder 51.37)
  - Mr. Edward Lorenz (Interview) — Executive Director, Career Development and Field Work, 1983 (Folder 51.38)
  - Campus Planning Committee, Sep 1984 (Folder 51.39)
  - Carnegie Mellon Consortium, 1983 (Folder 51.40)
  - Case Statement (VBS), 1981-1982 (Folder 51.41)
  - Center for Integrative Studies (Extra Copies of Proposal), May 1984 (Folder 51.42)
  - Christmas Cards, 1983-1984 (Folder 52.1)
  - Christmas Cards, 1982-1983 (Folder 52.2)
  - Christmas Cards, 1980-1981 (Folder 52.3)
  - Clippings, 1983-1984 (Folder 52.4)
  - Clippings, 1982-1983 (Folder 52.5)
  - Clippings, 1981-1982 (Folder 52.6)
  - College Center, 1980 (Folder 52.7)
  - College Council Breakfast Meeting, Oct 1983 (Folder 52.8)
  - College Council, 1979-1980 (Folder 52.9)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, 1983 (Folder 52.10)
  - College Law, 1982 (Folder 52.11)
  - Commencement — 1984, 1983-1984 (Folder 52.12)
  - Commencement Committee — 1983, 1982-1983 (Folder 52.13)
  - Commencement — 1983, 1982-1983 (Folder 52.14)
  - Commencement — 1982, 1981-1982 (Folder 52.15)
  - Commencement — 1981 — Luncheon after Graduation (Folder 52.16)
  - Commencement — 1981, 1980-1981 (Folder 52.17)
  - Commencement — 1980, 1979-1980 (Folder 52.18)
  - Commencement Committee — 1982, 1980-1982 (Folder 52.19)
  - Compensation, 1982 (Folder 52.20)
  - Computer Center Renovations, 1983 (Folder 52.21)
  - Computer User Committee, 1983-1984 (Folder 52.22)
  - Computer Planning, 1983-1984 (Folder 52.23)
  - Computerization Projects, 1982 (Folder 52.24)
  - Conference Board, 1982 (Folder 52.25)
  - Faculty Salary Scales, 1980 (Folder 52.26)
  - Federal Financial Aid, 1982 (Folder 52.27)
  - Ferry House Reunion (Follow-Up), 1982 (Folder 52.28)
  - Fee Schedule, 1981-1982 (Folder 52.29)
  - Food Committee Newsletter, 1981-1984 (Folder 52.30)